

Aalap Gandhi Transformation & Growth

≥ aalap.gandhi@gmail.com

L +91-7977084018

www.linkedin.com/in/aalap-gandhi/

• Mumbai

Technology is a perception. You have to have it right for you to resonate it for success; and the one not adapting with the changing time can not write the progress.

Thirteen years of rich experience in the blended mix of Sales, Strategy, Transformation & Brand Marketing.

Areas of Expertise

Sales Processes · Prospect Qualification · Account Management · Sales · Customer Satisfaction · GTM · Training Digital Transformation · Strategy · Large Scale Implementation · Product Lifecycle · LTV · Customer Acquisition Brand Marketing and Communication · Social Media · Networking · Presentations · Public Speaking Technology · BFSI · Insurance · Digital and Print Media · Beverage

Experience

Account Manager, Sales
 LUMIQ (Crisp Analytics Pvt Ltd)

Oct 2022 - Present, Mumbai

- Generating Revenue and Managing Accounts for Data and Analytics solutions
- New Business Development
 - Account Planning/Mapping & Pipeline Development
 - Identifying Opportunities and performing opportunity qualification assessment
 - Identifying key buyers and interacting with C level persona's
 - Analyzing business challenges and mapping it to products/solution offerings
 - Delivering presentations and assisting pre-sales during demonstrations
 - Seeking insights onto competition
 - Assisting in technical and commercial proposal preparation
 - Drive commercial discussions and negotiations
 - Work on various RFI's, RFP's & other closed invitation evaluation process
- Account Management
 - Develop & Mine strategic Accounts for other Business Cases and Technology Services
 - Creating Steady Pipeline
 - Perform Account and Strategic planning
 - · Periodic interactions with Business, Technology, Leadership, Procurement and other key entities
 - Ensuring customer satisfaction
 - Assist Delivery Team in existing Project execution
 - Candence Calls and Managing Escalations

AVP, Distribution Innovation and Strategy Future Generali India Life Insurance Company Ltd

Jun 2018 - Jul 2022, Mumbai

- 2 times Generali Asia Award Winner for Transformation in Distribution
- Lead team to enable DX Transformation across Agency, Direct Marketing, Bancasurance and Partnership Distribution
- Focused on Processes Digitalization to bring in efficiency and shorter TATs
- Launched and Managed E2E platform lifecycle for 4 key sales enablers POS, LMS, Agent Onboarding and BI Dashboard tools
- Managed Campaigns, Lead Management and Activity Management across business vertices
- Key Matrices Engagement, Activation and Conversion

DVP, Online Trading Business

Apr 2017 - Jun 2018, Mumbai

- Asit C Mehta Investment Interrmediates Ltd
- Lead the team of 12 to support Relaunch of Online Trading Platform
- · Managed online campaigns for Customer Acquisition
- Managed marketing campaigns for New Product Launches
- Supported development of new Online Trading Platform
- Integral part of the team which lead Process Enhancement across value chain
- · Lead Brand Refresh for Online Trading Platform
- · Managed Digital & Social Media Marketing for the brand

State Brand HeadDB Digital / DB Corp Ltd

Sep 2014 - Mar 2017, Ahmedabad

- Lead Mobile App Launch in Gujarat
- Achieved record 1.6 mn Download in first one month of launch
- Responsible for Online User Acquisition & Direct Traffic Growth (Web/Mobile)
- Managed Gujarat launch of New Brand Campaign
- Managed Brand Communication and Marketing for Digital and Print Media
- Managed marketing support while Relaunch of Vadodara Edition
- Lead Offline Marketing and Promotion Activities
- Supported Revenue Generation

State Trade Marketing Manager United Spirits Ltd (Diageo)

Jun 2010 - Feb 2013, Mumbai

- Managed Mumbai Region for all Customer Marketing Activities
- Provided marketing support to 40+ Sales personals
- Responsible to manage Outdoor and Onsight visibility drives
- · Managed three Brand launches
- · Managing promotional activities at On-Premise and Off-Premise

Certifications

- Oxford University Certificate Program in Fintech
- IBM Introduction to Cloud
- AWS Partner Sales Accreditation
- AWS Introduction to Cloud Adoption Framework
- Google Cloud- Sales Credentials
- Google Fundamentals of Digital Marketing

Education

• Post Graduation Diploma in Management Entrepreneurship Development Institute of India, Ahmedabad, Gujarat 2008-2010

• BSC Electronics Gujarat University, Ahmedabad, Gujarat 2005-2008